Aren't you afraid
that everything will happen again?
Sorry,
I forgot.
It's getting late.
Let's go back.
Chief Zhou,
I want to ask about Hengsheng.
Hello?
Mom, when is Dad coming back?
Your dad will be back soon.
You go study first.
Hello, Lawyer Li.
When exactly will my husband be released?
Don't tell me it's not optimistic.
I want to know the details.
Go ask for me right now.
Understood?
That's it.
Ah Long.
What exactly is going on?
Lingze betrayed the boss.
I need to send you abroad immediately
to prevent him from hurting you.
What about you guys?
Don't worry.
I'll arrange everything.
After you leave,
I'll take the blame.
Mr. Ling,
what should we do now?
I'm a little scared.
What are you panicking for?
It's just a little accident.
Keep an eye on them.
Everything goes according to plan.
Yes.
What a bunch of losers.
They can't even keep an eye on them.
Hello.
Attorney Gu.
I need your protection.
What happened?
It's Mr. Long.
He wants to take revenge on me.
Where are you now?
I'm in the car.
But I don't know where to go now.
Ling Heng and Shengsheng have both been taken.
What is he trying to do?
He's crazy.
He killed my mother and my brother.
Mucheng has also disappeared.
He wants to get rid of all of us.
He wants to seize all the property.
Please save me.
Why don't you come to us first?
Okay, okay.
I... I'll head over right now.
What's going on?
It's nothing, Mr. Ling.
Just a blind fool.
Do you know how to drive?
I'm asking you a question.
He's here.
Come save me!
Don't kill me.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Money, properties, I can give you everything.
Those who betray my father
must die.
You're just my father's dog.
No, no, no.
Don't kill me.
Do not destroy.
Do not destroy property.
Yeyu.
Chenyao.
Chenyao, are you okay?
Xingcan.
Never mind that.
I'll take you home.
Lingze.
Come help.
Don't just stand there.
Careful.
Help me hold him.
Come on.
Help me put him in.
Careful.
Go to the kitchen,
and get me a bucket of ice.
Okay.
Chenyao, Chenyao.
Chenyao, wake up.
Wake up.
Don't scare me, Chenyao.
Here's the ice.
Pour it in.
Pour it.
It's not enough. Get another bucket.
Hurry up.
Chenyao, Chenyao.
Lawyer Gu.
Is Brother Chen
okay?
Doesn't he need to go to the hospital?
No.
Then,
I'll go back and deal with the scene first.
Let's keep in touch.
Okay.
I'll be leaving then.
I never want to go back.
Then don't go back.
Then,
can I stay with you forever?
Of course.
Murderer.
Tang'er.
Xingcan.
Where is my dad?
Tell me.